

Alberto Sanchez Gutierrez

9 months Irata L1 and Blade Repair experience

Architect passionate about the vertical world and outdoors with an extensive experience from my role as climbing and canyoning guide and in the construction sector. Presently looking forward to embarking on a new adventure in Blade Repair

CONTACT:

Granada (Spain)

(+34) 646833708

albertosg.br@gmail.com

IRATA L1 N. 1/242783

WINDA N. AS055202ES

LANGUAGES:

spanish C2 ••••
english B2 •••
french B1 •••
italian B1 •••

SKILLS:

- Excellent at working in groups
- Works well under pressure
- Skillfull with hands working with different tools and materials
- o Comfortable working at heights
- Adaptable to new work environments
- Drive license type B
- Total availability for international geographic mobility

EXPERIENCE:

2024 - present April IRATA BLADE REPAIR TECHNICIAN

HMS High Maintenance Services | Albacete (Spain)

2023 - 2024 CLIMBING GYM CONSTRUCTION TECHNICIANVIVAC NATURE | *Granada (Spain)*

2021 - 2024 CLIMBING GUIDEGRANAVENTOUR | *Granada (Spain)*

2023 - 2024 CLIMBING & CANYONING GUIDE
VIVAC NATURE | Granada (Spain)

2019 - 2023 CLIMBING & CANYONING GUIDEEXPLORA AVENTURA | *Archidona, Málaga (Spain)*

2020 - 2022 CANYONING GUIDE

MOUNTAIN SPIRIT | Granada (Spain)

2021 - 2022 CANYONING GUIDETITAN AVENTURA | *Granada (Spain)*

2018 - 2019 CANYONING GUIDE

RODELLAR AVENTURA | Rodellar, Huesca (Spain)

2018 - 2018 CANYONING GUIDERUMBO AVENTURA | *Alquezar, Huesca (Spain)*

WIND TURBINE EXPERIENCE:

- Working around 9 months in HMS in Spain and Europe
- Blade Repair in tip, root, leading and trailing edges & nacelle
- Tower & hub repairing and paints
- Installations and Replacements of Aviation Lights & Serrations
- Replacements of LPS (Diverter strip & Graphite receptor)
- Blades boroscopies detecting damages
- o Construction of the turbins, tower, blades, and wires
- Some **certifications** of elevators and security lines.
- Wind Turbines General Electric GE Cypress, 4x, 3x, 2x and 1x



Alberto Sanchez Gutierrez

9 months Irata L1 and Blade Repair experience

Architect passionate about the vertical world and outdoors with an extensive experience from my role as climbing and canyoning guide and in the construction sector. Presently looking forward to embarking on a new adventure in Blade Repair

CONTACT:

Granada (Spain)

(+34) 646833708

albertosg.br@gmail.com

IRATA L1 N. 1/242783

WINDA N. AS055202ES

LANGUAGES:

spanish C2 ••••

english B2 •••

french B1 ••

italian B1 ••

SKILLS:

- Excellent at working in groups
- Works well under pressure
- Skillfull with hands working with different tools and materials
- o Comfortable working at heights
- Adaptable to new work environments
- O Drive license type B
- Total availability for international geographic mobility

EDUCATION:

2024	GWO BLADE REPAIR MUCHO VERTICAL <i>Jérez de la Frontera, Cádiz (Spain)</i>
2023	ROPE ACCESS TECHNICIAN LEVEL 1 (>500 hours worked) MUCHO VERTICAL Jérez de la Frontera, Cádiz (Spain)
2023	MASTER IN TEACHERS UCAM Murcia (Spain)
2021	SPORT TECHNICIAN IN CLIMBING LEVEL 2 (TD2) IAD Málaga (Spain)
2018	SPORT TECHNICIAN IN CANYONING LEVEL 2 (TD2) IUNDENIA Granada (Spain)
2017	BACHELOR OF ARQUITECTURE UNIVERSIDAD DE GRANADA Granada (Spain)

COURSES:

Electrical Safety Advanced

assembly of metal structures

(20 hours) PREVECAM | Albacete (Spain)

2024 06

202100	GE VERNOVA
2024 06	Electrical Service Bulletin GE VERNOVA
2024 06	Climb Assist User GE VERNOVA
2024 06	Confined Space Awareness GE VERNOVA
2024 06	Hand and Power Tools GE VERNOVA
2024 06	GE VERNOVA
2024 06	Stop Work GE VERNOVA
2024 05	Occupational Risk Prevention (24 hours) PADRONE AIFOS Rome (Italy)
2024 04	Occupational Risk Prevention in Installation, repair and